( all groaning )
OH, MONICA,
THAT WAS THE BEST
THANKSGIVING DINNER EVER.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
I THINK YOU KILLED US.
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY
EAT ANOTHER BITE.
I NEED SOMETHING SWEET.
DOES ANYONE WANT TO WATCH TV?
All:
YEAH.
MONICA, YOUR REMOTE
DOESN'T WORK.
PHOEBE, YOU HAVE
TO LIFT IT AND POINT.
OH.
OH, FORGET IT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT
WE SHOULD ALL DO?
WE SHOULD PLAY THAT GAME
WHERE EVERYONE SAYS
ONE THING THAT
THEY'RE THANKFUL FOR.
OH, I... I AM THANKFUL
FOR THIS BEAUTIFUL FALL
WE'VE BEEN HAVING.
THAT'S SWEET, JOEY.
VERY NICE.
YEAH, THE OTHER DAY
I WAS AT THE BUS STOP
AND THIS LOVELY FALL BREEZE
CAME IN OUT OF NOWHERE
AND BLEW THIS CHICK'S SKIRT
RIGHT UP.
OH, WHICH REMINDS ME
I'M ALSO THANKFUL FOR THONGS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU ♪
♪ LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
SO MUCH AN UNDERPANT
AS IT IS A FEAT OF ENGINEERING.
IT'S AMAZING
HOW MUCH THEY CAN DO
WITH SO LITTLE MATERIAL.
YOU KNOW, AND THE WAY
THEY PLAY WITH YOUR MIND.
I MEAN, IS IT THERE?
IS IT NOT THERE?
( mumbling )
ARE YOU AWARE THAT
YOU'RE STILL TALKING?
IS ANYONE THANKFUL
FOR ANYTHING ELSE
BESIDES A THONG?
HUH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO PICK.
AM I MORE THANKFUL
FOR MY DIVORCE
OR MY EVICTION?
WOW. SEE, AND I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE ABLE TO COME UP
WITH ANYTHING.
I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST
THIS IS THE WORST
THANKSGIVING EVER.
NO, NO, NO, NO. I AM THE KING
OF BAD THANKSGIVINGS.
YOU CAN'T JUST SWOOP IN HERE
WITH YOUR BAD MARRIAGE
AND TAKE THAT AWAY FROM ME.
NO, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL
THE WHOLE STORY
ABOUT HOW YOUR PARENTS
GOT DIVORCED AGAIN, ARE YOU?
OH, GOD NO.
NO, NO, COME ON,
I WANT TO HEAR IT.
IT WOULDN'T BE THANKSGIVING
WITHOUT CHANDLER BUMMING US OUT.
IT'S A TRADITION
LIKE THE PARADE...
IF THE PARADE DECIDED
IT WAS GAY, MOVED OUT
AND ABANDONED
ITS ENTIRE FAMILY.
NOW, CHANDLER, DEAR,
JUST BECAUSE
YOUR FATHER AND I
ARE GETTING A DIVORCE
DOESN'T MEAN
WE DON'T LOVE YOU.
IT JUST MEANS
HE WOULD RATHER SLEEP
WITH THE HOUSEBOY
THAN WITH ME.
MORE TURKEY,
MR. CHANDLER?
YOU'RE RIGHT,
YOURS IS WORSE.
YOU ARE THE KING OF
BAD THANKSGIVINGS.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I'VE GOT ONE THAT'S WORSE.
REALLY? WORSE THAN
"MORE TURKEY, MR. CHANDLER?"
OH, DID THE
LITTLE RICH BOY
HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THE BUTLER?
YES, MINE'S WORSE.
MORE BANDAGES! MORE BANDAGES!
PLEASE, CAN I GET
SOME MORE BANDAGES IN HERE?!
THIS MAN IS DYING!
OH, NO.
IN THIS LIFE, PHOEBE.
OH, THIS LIFE.
OH, OKAY.
NO, CHANDLER'S IS WORSE.
MAN, IT MUST
BE SO COOL,
REMEMBERING STUFF
LIKE THAT.
I DON'T HAVE ANY
PAST LIFE MEMORIES.
OF COURSE YOU
DON'T, SWEETIE.
YOU'RE BRAND NEW.
I KNOW MONICA'S
WORST THANKSGIVING.
LET'S NOT TELL
THIS STORY.
OH, COME ON.
OH, NO. I KNOW,
I KNOW.
IT'S THE ONE WHERE JOEY
GOT MONICA'S TURKEY
STUCK ON HIS HEAD.
WHAT?
WHAT?!
JOEY GOT A TURKEY
STUCK ON HIS HEAD?
HEY, IT'S NOT
LIKE IT SOUNDS.
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE IT SOUNDS.
( muffled ):
HELLO?
PHOEBE?
JOEY? WHAT'S GOING ON?
( Phoebe gasps )
OH, MY GOD!
I KNOW.
IT'S STUCK!
STEP.
HOW DID IT GET ON?
I PUT IT ON
TO SCARE CHANDLER.
OH, MY GOD!
MONICA'S GOING TO
TOTALLY FREAK OUT.
WELL, THEN HELP ME
GET IT OFF.
PLUS, IT SMELLS
REALLY BAD IN HERE.
OF COURSE IT
SMELLS REALLY BAD.
YOU HAVE YOUR HEAD
UP A DEAD ANIMAL.
OOH, OH. MONICA.
HEY.
HEY, DID YOU GET
THE TURKEY BASTE...?
OH, MY GOD!
WHO IS THAT?
IT'S JOEY.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
NO, IT'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE FUNNY.
IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE SCARY.
WELL, GET THAT
OFF NOW.
I CAN'T. IT'S STUCK.
I DON'T CARE. THAT HAS TO FEED
20 PEOPLE AT MY PARENTS' HOUSE
AND THEY'RE NOT GOING TO EAT IT
OFF YOUR HEAD!
HOLD ON, OKAY?
LET'S JUST ALL THINK.
OKAY, I GOT IT.
PHOEBE, YOU PULL.
I'M GOING TO SPREAD
THE LEGS AS WIDE AS I CAN.
( snickering )
JOEY?
YEAH.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
SORRY. RIGHT. SORRY.
OKAY, ON THE COUNT OF THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
( yelling )
IT WORKED.
I SCARED YOU.
I KNEW IT.
HA-HA!
I'M OVER HERE, BIG GUY.
YEAH, YOU ARE.
YEAH, HA-HA!
I SCARED YOU.
( whooping )
YOU-YOU DID LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
HEY, I WASN'T THE ONLY ONE WHO
LOOKED LIKE AN IDIOT, ALL RIGHT?
REMEMBER WHEN ROSS
TRIED TO SAY "BUTTERNUT SQUASH"
AND IT CAME OUT...
"SQUATTER NUTBOSH"?
YEAH, THAT'S
THE SAME.
WELL, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S MY WORST THANKSGIVING.
OH, WAIT. THAT CAN'T BE THE ONE
THAT RACHEL WAS TALKING ABOUT
'CAUSE SHE DIDN'T EVEN
KNOW THAT THAT HAPPENED.
Joey: OH, RIGHT.
Ross: WHAT WAS IT?
I-I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO TELL THIS STORY.
OH, COME ON, MONICA.
RELIVING PAST PAIN
AND GETTING DEPRESSED
IS WHAT THANKSGIVING'S
ALL ABOUT.
YOU KNOW,
FOR ME ANYWAY.
AND, OF COURSE,
THE INDIANS.
LOOK, UM, OF ALL PEOPLE
YOU DO NOT WANT ME
TO TELL THIS STORY.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
( doorbell ringing )
MONICA! I THINK RACHEL IS HERE.
Monica:
I'LL GET IT!
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
NOT FOR ME.
CHIP AND I BROKE UP.
WHY? WHY? WELL,
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, YOU KNOW HOW
MY PARENTS ARE OUT OF TOWN
AND CHIP WAS GOING
TO COME OVER?
YEAH, YEAH, AND
YOU WERE GOING
TO GIVE HIM,
YOU KNOW...
YOUR FLOWER.
OKAY, MONICA,
CAN YOU JUST CALL IT "SEX"?
IT REALLY CREEPS ME OUT
WHEN YOU CALL IT THAT.
OKAY, AND BY THE WAY,
WHILE WE'RE AT IT
A GUY'S THING IS NOT
CALLED HIS "TENDERNESS."
BELIEVE ME.
HI.
HI, RACHEL.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
YOU TOO, SWEETHEART.
HEY.
OH, HI.
UH... EVERYONE
THIS IS CHANDLER,
MY ROOMMATE
AND LEAD SINGER
OF OUR BAND.
ROSS.
OH, THIS IS MONICA.
HI, I'M ROSS'S
LITTLE SISTER.
OKAY.
I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD COME,
CHANDLER.
WE GOT PLENTY OF FOOD,
SO I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
OH, MOM, CHANDLER
HATES THANKSGIVING
AND DOESN'T EAT ANY
THANKSGIVING FOOD.
OH. OH, I'M SO GLAD
YOU BROUGHT HIM HERE, THEN.
HEY, CHANDLER, UM...
IF YOU WANT, I CAN MAKE YOU
SOME MACARONI
AND CHEESE FOR DINNER.
WELL, AS LONG AS THE PILGRIMS
DIDN'T EAT IT, THEN I'M IN.
( laughs, snorts soda )
DAMN IT.
SO, UH..., RACHE
DOES IT, DOES IT FEEL
WEIRD AROUND HERE NOW?
YOU KNOW, SINCE I'VE
BEEN AWAY AT COLLEGE?
OH. NO, NOT REALLY.
WELL, THAT'S COOL.
SO DO...?
OH!
I CANNOT BELIEVE
CHIP DUMPED ME
FOR THAT SLUT
NANCY BRANSON.
I AM NEVER GOING OUT
WITH HIM AGAIN, YOU KNOW.
I DON'T CARE HOW
MUCH HE BEGS.
I THINK HIS BEGGING DAYS
ARE OVER
NOW HE'S GOING OUT
WITH NANCY BRANSON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE JUST HAD IT
WITH HIGH SCHOOL BOYS.
THEY'RE JUST... SILLY.
THEY'RE JUST SILLY,
STUPID BOYS.
I'M GOING TO START DATING MEN.
UH, I'M SORRY, JUDY.
I COULDN'T FIND THAT BOWL
YOU AND JACK WERE LOOKING FOR.
( scoffs ):
CALL THEM "MOM AND DAD,"
YOU LOSER.
( whines ):
MONICA!
HEY, CHANDLER...
DID YOU LIKE
THE MACARONI AND CHEESE?
OH, YEAH. IT WAS GREAT.
YOU SHOULD BE A CHEF.
OKAY.
GUESS WHAT?
ALL THIS STUFF
ABOUT NANCY BRANSON
BEING A SLUT WAS ALL A RUMOR,
SO CHIP DUMPED HER
AND HE WANTS TO COME OVER
TO MY HOUSE TONIGHT.
OH, THAT IS SO GREAT!
OH, GOSH, LISTEN.
IF YOU AND CHIP
DO IT TONIGHT
PROMISE ME YOU'LL
TELL ME EVERYTHING.
OH, TOTALLY, TOTALLY. YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
WE ALREADY KIND OF
DID IT ONCE, YOU KNOW.
I KNOW, BUT THIS
TIME YOU'RE GOING
TO DEFINITELY KNOW
WHETHER OR NOT
YOU DID IT.
I KNOW. OH, AND CHIP PROMISED
THAT-THAT THIS TIME
IT WOULD LAST
AT LEAST FOR AN ENTIRE SONG.
SO I'M THINKING OF ASKING
RACHEL OUT TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
PLAYING HER THAT SONG
WE WROTE LAST WEEK.
"EMOTIONAL KNAPSACK"?
YEAH.
RIGHT ON.
OH, BUT DON'T TAKE
TOO LONG, OKAY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE GOING TO TEST OUT
OUR FAKE I.D.s TONIGHT,
RIGHT, CLIFFORD ALVEREZ?
LISTEN, ROWLAND CHENG...
IF THINGS GO WELL, I MAY
BE OUT WITH HER ALL NIGHT.
DUDE, DON'T DO THAT TO ME.
NO, IT'S COOL.
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
MY PARENTS WON'T MIND.
NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BE STUCK HERE
ALL NIGHT WITH
YOUR FAT SISTER.
HEY.
MONICA, WHY DON'T YOU
FINISH OFF THESE PIES?
I DON'T HAVE ANY MORE
ROOM IN THE FRIDGE.
NO.
NO, THANK YOU.
WELL, JUDY, YOU DID IT.
SHE'S FINALLY FULL.
I CALLED YOU FAT?
I DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER THAT.
WELL, I DO.
I'M SO SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
BUT, COME ON, I WAS
AN IDIOT BACK THEN.
I RUSHED THE STAGE
AT A WHAM! CONCERT,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CALLED HER FAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET
GEORGE MICHAEL SLAP YOU.
I AM REALLY SORRY.
THAT IS SO TERRIBLE.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT THE THANKSGIVING
I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
YES, IT WAS.
NO, IT WASN'T.
IT WAS ACTUALLY...
THANKSGIVING'S OVER.
LET'S GET READY FOR CHRISTMAS.
WHO WANTS TO GO GET
A CHRISTMAS TREE?
OOH, NO. I HAVE THE
CUTEST CHRISTMAS STORY.
BUT WE WANT
TO HEAR MONICA'S
THANKSGIVING STORY.
FINE. ALL RIGHT.
MINE HAD A DWARF
THAT GOT BROKE IN HALF
BUT, YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
SO, RACHEL, YOUR MOM TELLS ME
YOU CHANGED YOUR MAJOR AGAIN.
WELL, YEAH, I HAD TO.
THERE WAS NEVER ANY PARKING
BY THE PSYCHOLOGY BUILDING.
HI, RACHEL.
OH, HI.
WOW, LOVE
YOUR NEW NOSE.
JACK...
WHAT? DR. WILSON'S
AN ARTIST.
HE REMOVED MY MOLE CLUSTER.
WANT TO SEE?
( doorbell rings )
I'LL GET IT.
NO, GOD. PLEASE LET ME.
HEY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
HI.
GOD, YOUR HAIR
SURE IS DIFFERENT.
YEAH, WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW STUPID WE USED TO LOOK.
YEAH.
SO, UH, WHERE'S MONICA?
SHE'S UPSTAIRS.
MONICA, COME DOWN.
EVERYONE'S HERE--
ROSS, RACHEL
AND THE BOY
WHO HATES THANKSGIVING.
HI, CHANDLER.
OH, MY GOD.
W-W-WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IS THERE...
IS THERE SOMETHING
ON MY DRESS?
YOU LOOK SO DIFFERENT,
TERRIFIC.
THAT DRESS, THAT BODY.
DUDE.
SORRY.
YES, YES. MONICA IS THIN.
IT'S WONDERFUL,
BUT WHAT WE REALLY
WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
IS ROSS'S NEW GIRLFRIEND.
OH, MOM.
OKAY. UM,
HER NAME IS CAROL
AND SHE'S REALLY PRETTY
AND SMART
AND, UH, SHE'S...
SHE'S ON THE LACROSSE TEAM
AND THE GOLF TEAM,
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
SHE PLAYS FOR BOTH TEAMS.
SO, CHANDLER, I GUESS
I'LL SEE YOU AT DINNER.
DUDE.
SORRY.
OH, MY GOD. THAT
WAS SO AWESOME.
YOU TOTALLY GOT HIM BACK
FOR CALLING YOU FAT.
HE WAS JUST DROOLING
ALL OVER YOU.
THAT MUST HAVE
FELT SO GREAT.
WELL, IT DIDN'T.
WHAT?
YEAH. I MEAN,
YEAH, I LOOK GREAT
AND, YEAH, I FEEL GREAT,
AND, YEAH, MY HEART'S
NOT IN TROUBLE ANYMORE,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I JUST DON'T FEEL
LIKE I GOT HIM BACK, YOU KNOW?
I JUST WANT TO HUMILIATE HIM.
I WANT TO...
I WANT HIM TO BE LIKE NAKED
AND I WANT TO POINT AT HIM
AND I WANT TO LAUGH.
OKAY.
THAT WE MAY
BE ABLE TO DO.
HOW?
WELL, GUYS
TEND TO GET NAKED
BEFORE THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE SEX.
WHAT?!
I DIDN'T WORK THIS HARD
A-A-AND LOSE ALL THIS WEIGHT
JUST SO I COULD GIVE MY FLOWER
TO SOMEONE LIKE HIM.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, IF
YOU KEEP CALLING IT THAT
NO ONE'S EVER
GOING TO TAKE IT.
AND THEN,
SECOND OF ALL
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO ACTUALLY
HAVE SEX WITH HIM.
YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO MAKE HIM THINK
THAT YOU ARE.
YEAH.
AND THEN WHEN HE'S NAKED,
I CAN THROW HIM OUT
IN THE FRONT YARD
AND LOCK THE DOOR,
AND THEN ALL OUR NEIGHBORS
WILL JUST HUMILIATE HIM.
YEAH, AND THEN YOU WILL
DEFINITELY GET HIM BACK.
HOW DO I MAKE HIM THINK
I WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH HIM?
UH, HERE'S
WHAT YOU DO.
JUST ACT LIKE EVERYTHING
AROUND YOU TURNS YOU ON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, LIKE ANYTHING
CAN BE SEXY,
LIKE, UM...
OH! OKAY, LIKE THIS...
LIKE THIS DISHTOWEL.
OOH... OOH...
THIS FEELS SO GOOD
AGAINST MY CHEEK.
AND IF I GET A LITTLE HOT,
I CAN JUST DAB MYSELF WITH IT.
OR I CAN BRING IT
DOWN TO MY SIDE
AND MAYBE RUN IT
THROUGH MY FINGERS
WHILE I TALK TO HIM.
I CAN DO THAT.
YEAH? OKAY, GOOD, GOOD.
HE'S COMING.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
HEY.
MONICA, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD MAKE ME
SOME OF THAT RIGHTEOUS
MAC 'N' CHEESE
LIKE LAST YEAR.
UH, I'D LOVE TO.
OOH... I LOVE
MACARONI AND CHEESE.
I LOVE... I LOVE
THE WAY THIS BOX FEELS
AGAINST MY CHEEK.
OKAY.
OH, AND I LOVE CARROTS.
OH...
SOMETIMES I LIKE TO PUT THEM
BETWEEN MY FINGERS...
LIKE THIS, AND... AND...
AND HOLD THEM DOWN HERE
WHILE I TALK TO YOU.
UM, AN-AN-AND YOU KNOW,
IF I GET REALLY HOT?
UM, I-I LIKE TO...
PICK UP THIS KNIFE
AND... AND, UM,
I PUT THE...
THE COOL STEEL
AGAINST, UM...
MY BODY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
I'M FINE. IT'S...
WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
20-YEAR-OLD MALE.
HE'S GOT A SEVERED TOE
ON HIS RIGHT FOOT.
OW! OW!
COULD YOU PLEASE NOT
DO THAT FEET-FIRST?
YOU KNOW
WHERE HIS INJURY IS.
SEVERED TOE.
YOU JUST SAID IT!
SAYS HERE THE KNIFE
WENT RIGHT THROUGH YOUR SHOE.
OF COURSE IT DID.
THEY'RE MADE OF WICKER.
DID YOU BRING
THE TOE?
OH, YES. I HAVE IT
RIGHT HERE ON ICE.
DON'T WORRY, SON, WE'LL
JUST REATTACH IT AND THEN...
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
YOU BROUGHT A CARROT.
WHAT?
THIS ISN'T YOUR TOE.
THIS IS A SMALL,
VERY COLD PIECE OF CARROT.
YOU BROUGHT
A CARROT?
OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S A TOE
IN MY KITCHEN.
GOD, I'M SORRY!
I'LL GO BACK AND GET IT!
IT'S TOO LATE. ALL WE CAN DO NOW
IS SEW UP THE WOUND.
WITHOUT MY TOE?
I NEED MY TOE.
WHAT? NO, NO.
I CAN GO REALLY FAST.
DAD, GIVE ME THE
KEYS TO YOUR PORSCHE.
OH, I'M NOT FALLING
FOR THAT ONE.
THAT'S WHY I LOST MY TOE?
BECAUSE I CALLED YOU FAT?
I DIDN'T MEAN TO CUT IT OFF.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
THAT'S WHY, FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR
PEOPLE CALLED ME
SIR LIMPS-A-LOT?
I'M SORRY.
IT WASN'T YOUR WHOLE TOE.
YEAH, WELL,
I MISS THE TIP.
IT'S THE BEST PART.
IT HAS THE NAIL.
CHANDLER...
SIR LIMPS-A-LOT--
I CAME UP WITH THAT.
YOU'RE A DORK.
( sighing ):
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
CHANDLER, I SAID
I WAS SORRY.
YEAH? WELL, SORRY
DOESN'T BRING BACK
THE LITTLE PIGGY
THAT CRIED ALL THE WAY HOME.
I HATE THIS STUPID DAY
AND EVERYTHING ABOUT IT.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OH, WAIT, CHANDLER.
COME HERE. IS THERE
ANYTHING I CAN DO?
ANYTHING?
YEAH, JUST... LEAVE ME ALONE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
OH, OH, I'M A DUCK.
I GO, "QUACK, QUACK."
I'M HAPPY ALL THE TIME.
( knocking )
NICE TRY.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
LOOK, MONICA...
THIS IS NOT GOING TO WORK.
I BET THIS WILL WORK.
( laughing )
YOU ARE SO GREAT.
I LOVE YOU.
WHAT?
NOTHING. I SAID...
I SAID, "YOU'RE SO GREAT,"
AND THEN I JUST...
I JUST STOPPED TALKING.
YOU SAID YOU LOVED ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU LOVE ME.
NO, I DON'T!
STOP IT! STOP IT!
( screaming )
GAUZE! GAUZE!
I NEED TO GET
SOME GAUZE IN HERE!
CAN I PLEASE GET
SOME MORE GAUZE?!
( explosion )
PHEW!
THIS IS GETTING RIDICULOUS, HUH?
OKAY. ALORS.